<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">A Test Library</string>

    <style name="AppTheme"></style>

    <string name="stretch"> \"When my father built Bald Hills he thought the place was his: his
land, his air, his peasants. But Napoleon came and swept him aside,
unconscious of his existence, as he might brush a chip from his
path, and his Bald Hills and his whole life fell to pieces. Princess
Mary says it is a trial sent from above. What is the trial for, when
he is not here and will never return? He is not here! For whom then is
the trial intended? The Fatherland, the destruction of Moscow! And
tomorrow I shall be killed, perhaps not even by a Frenchman but by one
of our own men, by a soldier discharging a musket close to my ear as
one of them did yesterday, and the French will come and take me by
head and heels and fling me into a hole that I may not stink under
their noses, and new conditions of life will arise, which will seem
quite ordinary to others and about which I shall know nothing. I shall
not exist\"</string>
    <string name="text">TEXT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_screen">ScreenActivity</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string-array name="snippets">
        <item >Copyright laws are changing all over the world</item>
        <item >Copyright laws are changing all over the world. Be sure to check the\ncopyright</item>
        <item >Please read the \"legal small print,\" and other information about the
eBook and Project Gutenberg at the bottom of this file.  Included is
important information about your specific rights and restrictions in
how the file may be used.  You can also find out about how to make a
donation to Project Gutenberg, and how to get involved.</item>
        <item >No, my brougham is waiting</item>
        <item >_Clinically_ the disease is attended with the gradual and painless
development during childhood or adolescence of a number of tumours or
irregular projections of bone, at the ends of the long bones, the
vertebral border of the scapula, and the cristal border of the ilium.
They exhibit a rough symmetry; they rarely attain any size; and they
usually cease growing when the skeleton attains maturity--the conversion</item>
        <item >_Clinically_ the disease is attended with the gradual and painless
development during childhood or adolescence of a number of tumours or
irregular projections of bone, at the ends of the long bones, the
vertebral border of the scapula, and the cristal border of the ilium.
They exhibit a rough symmetry; they rarely attain any size; and they
usually cease growing when the skeleton attains maturity--the conversion
of cartilage into bone being then completed. While they originate from
the ossifying junctions of the long bones, they tend, as the shaft
increases in length, to project from the surface of the bone at some
distance from the ossifying junction and to \"point\" away from it. They
may cause symptoms by \"lockingCopyright laws are changing all over the world. Be sure to check the
copyright laws for your country before downloading or redistributing
this or any other Project Gutenberg eBook the adjacent joint or by pressing upon
nerve-trunks or blood vessels.</item>
        <item >Sarasate plays at the St. James\'s Hall this afternoon</item>
        <item >When Natasha had been told that morning that Prince Andrew was
seriously wounded and was traveling with their party, she had at first
asked many questions: Where was he going? How was he wounded? Was it
serious? And could she see him? But after she had been told that she
could not see him, that he was seriously wounded but that his life was
not in danger, she ceased to ask questions or to speak at all,</item>
        <item >When Natasha had been told that morning that Prince Andrew was
seriously wounded and was traveling with their party, she had at first
asked many questions: Where was he going? How was he wounded? Was it
serious? And could she see him? But after she had been told that she
could not see him, that he was seriously wounded but that his life was
not in danger, she ceased to ask questions or to speak at all,
evidently disbelieving what they told her, and convinced that say what
she might she would still be told the same. All the way she had sat
motionless in a corner of the coach with wide open eyes, and the
expression in them which the countess knew so well and feared so much,
and now she sat in the same way on the bench where she had seated
herself on arriving. She was planning something and either deciding or
had already decided something in her mind. The countess knew this, but
what it might be she did not know, and this alarmed and tormented her.</item>_ClinicallyWhen Natasha had been told that morning that Prince Andrew was
seriously wounded and was traveling with their party, she had at first the disease is attended with the gradual and painless
development during childhood or adolescence of a number of tumours or_Clinically_ the disease is attended with the gradual and painless
development during childhood or adolescence of a number of tumours or
irregular projections of bone, at the ends of the long bones, the
vertebral border of the scapula, and the cristal border of the ilium.
They exhibit a rough symmetry; they rarely attain any size; and they
usually cease growing when the skeleton attains maturity--the conversion
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="webSites">
        <item >http://www.google.com.br</item>
        <item >http://www.amazon.com</item>
        <item >http://www.uol.com.br</item>
        <item >http://www.huffingtonpost.com</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="light_test">
        <item >First Label</item>
        <item >Second Label</item>
        <item >Thirth Label</item>
        <item >Button</item>
    </string-array>
        <string name="first_label">First Label</string>
        <string name="second_label">Second Label</string>
        <string name="third_label">Third Label</string>
        <string name="button_label">Button Label</string>
        <string name="MultiAutoCompleteTextView">Multi Auto Complete Text View</string>
        <string name="fourth_label">Fourth Label</string>
        <string name="fifth_label">Fifth Label</string>
        <string name="sixth_label">Sixth Label</string>
        <string name="button_label2">Button Label 2</string>
        <string name="button_label3">Button Label 3</string>
        <string name="seventh_label">Seventh Label</string>
        <string name="eighth_label">Eighth Label</string>
        <string name="nineth_label">Ninth Label</string>
        <string name="tenth_label">Tenth Label</string>
        <string name="eleventh_label">Eleventh Label</string>
        <string name="check_label">Check Option</string>
        <string name="radio_label">Radio Option</string>
        <string name="start_button">Start test</string>

</resources>
